

AKHIL MAMODIYA

DATASTAGE DEVELOPER

CONTACT

+91-9987612259

akhil.mamodiya@gmail.com

Gurugram, Haryana

in Linkedin.com/in/amamodiya

EDUCATION

B. TECH in Computer Engg. Rajasthan Technical University 2009-2013 Score:71.08%

HSC Nutan Vidya Mandir ,Jaipur 2007-2008 Score:82.31%

SSC Adarsh Vidya Mandir, Jaipur 2005-2006 Score:87.17%

SKILLS

- Datastage
- Unix
- PL SQL
- Autosys
- Talend
- Oracle
- SQL Server
- Netezza
- DB2

ABOUT ME

ETL/BI professional with over 6 year of experience in data warehouse and end to end application development projects using both waterfall and agile methodology across banking, healthcare and manufacturing domain.

Experience in complete life cycle development process including requirement analysis, development, testing, Implementation, maintenance and documentation.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Application Developer Senior Analyst Accenture Solutions Pvt. Ltd. | Gurugram, Haryana | Oct 2019-Till Date

- Recognized business needs, evaluated business and technical alternatives, suggested solutions and took part in their implementation.
- Constantly interacted with business users to discuss requirements.
- Designed and developed parallel jobs using datastage designer as per the mapping specifications using appropriate stages.
- Created autosys jils for scheduling Datastage jobs.

Technology Analyst

Infosys Ltd. | Chandigarh, Punjab | Oct 2018-Oct 2019

- Involved in understanding of business processes to learn business requirements.
- Designed and developed datastage jobs to extract data from heterogeneous sources, applied transform logics to extracted data and Loaded into data Warehouse Databases.
- Involved in unit, performance and integration testing of datastage jobs.

System Engineer

Tata Consultancy Services Ltd. | Mumbai, Maharashtra | Apr 2016-Sept 2018

- Converted all server jobs of application into parallel.
- Understanding existing datastage jobs for enhancements to accomplish new requirements.
- Provided Production support and performed enhancement on existing multiple projects.
- Created shell script to run data stage jobs from UNIX and then schedule this script to run data stage jobs through Cron Tab.

Software Engineer

Syntel Ltd. | Mumbai, Maharashtra | Dec 2013-Apr 2016

- Written packages, procedures and functions to populate data in database.
- Developed several parallel jobs to load data from sequential files and MS SQL Server.
- Conversion of some ETL jobs to stored procedures in MS SQL Server.
- Performed Unit testing and system integration testing in DEV and UAT environments.